[{"id": 2076, "question": "The United States government has decided that food from cloned cattle, pigs and goats is safe to eat. The Food and Drug Administration also says it found no risks in meat and milk from cloned animals. The F.D.A. looked at studies for several years before it announced its decision in a final report this month. The United States Department of Agriculture supported the findings. But it says time is needed to clear the way for marketing meat and milk from clones. The F.D.A. will not require any product to be registered as coming from clones. A producer would need to label a product \"clone-free\". The agency says that could be misunderstood because the food is not different from other food. But activists argue that the F.D.A. based its decision on incomplete research into possible risks. The Cen...\n\nQ: What is the best title for this passage?", "options": ["Is Food from Cloned Animals Safe?", "A New Clone Policy", "A Big Danger --Cloned Food", "Cloned Products --A Terrible Choice"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3102, "question": "One of India's great economic advantages is the youth of its population. To make the most of this advantage, India's children need to be educated. On paper, India is doing well here. The country has a nationwide network of state primary schools funded by a specially designed tax. 96% of children aged 6-14 go to school, even in rural areas. That's well above the average for the developing world and their attendance is good. But the attainment is poor: three quarters of third graders can't read a gradeone text and 53% of grade five kids can't read at the standard they should have achieved at grade two. Levels of achievement are almost as bad in math. \"The main problem in India is not school entry or whether there is a local school; it's the delivery of education, the way teaching is done or ...\n\nQ: What can be inferred about the Read India programme?", "options": ["It encourages more kids to attend school.", "It improves the quality of India's education.", "It is in the charge of management committees.", "It helps improve the basic facilities of schooling."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2830, "question": "It has been argued that an infant under three who is cared for outside the home may suffer because of the separation from his parents.The British psychoanalyst John Bowlby believes that separation from the parents during the sensitive \"attachment\" period from birth to three may scar a child's personality and incline to emotional problems in later life.Some people have drawn the conclusion from Bowlby's work that children should not be sent to day care before the age of three, and many people do believe this.But there are also arguments against such a strong conclusion. Firstly, anthropologists point out that the hidden love between children and parents found in modem societies does not usually exist in traditional societies.For example, we saw earlier that among the Ngonis the father and m...\n\nQ: This passage is mainly talking about  _  .", "options": ["children's personality", "advantages of infants' early care", "infants' education", "negative effect of infant school"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1082, "question": "It's 5pm on a Friday and I'm standing in a coffee shop above Shibuya crossing - one of the most busiest place in Japan where more than a thousand of Tokyo's smartly dressed people gather at eight points, ready to cross - then rush straight for each other. It looks like they must bump into each other, but It's amazing that they all manage to reach the other side safely. But the real reason I'm here is that I want to see people crash. I want businessmen to knock into each other, their umbrellas flying off their arms, and uniformed schoolchildren hitting grannies. Why may I see this now, but wouldn't have had the chance even a year ago? It's very simple - smartphones. Smartphone use is booming in Japan. In 2012, only about a quarter of Japanese used them, most being perfectly happy with their...\n\nQ: How does the author confirm whether smartphone walk is annoying or not?", "options": ["By personal experimenting", "By comparing with other way of walk", "By giving example.", "By explaining the traffic rules patiently"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3009, "question": "To me, life without music would not be exciting. I realize that this is not true for everybody. Many people get along quite well without going to the concert, and listening to the record. But music plays an important part in everyone's life, whether he realizes it or not. Try to imagine, for example, what films or TV plays would be like without music. Would the feelings, the moving plot, and the greatest interests, be so exciting or dramatic? I'm not sure about it. Now, we have been speaking of music in its more common meaning----the kind of music we hear in the concert hall. But if we look at some parts of music more closely, we discover them in our everyday life too----in the rhythm of the sea, the _ of a bird in the woods and so on. So music surely has meaning for everyone, in some way ...\n\nQ: What dose the writer say more about in the text?", "options": ["Life full of music.", "Life without music.", "The importance of music.", "The development of music."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1463, "question": "I have only once been in trouble with the law.The whole process of being arrested and taken to court was a rather unpleasant experience at the time, but it makes a good story now. What makes it rather disturbing was the arbitrary circumstances both of my arrest and my subsequent fate in court. It happened in February about twelve years ago.I had left school a couple of months before that and was not due to go to university until the following October.I was still living at home at the time. One morning I was in Richmond, a suburb of London near where I lived.I was looking for a temporary job so that I could save up some money to go traveling.As it was a fine day and I was in no hurry, I was taking my time, looking in shop windows, strolling in the park, and sometimes just stopping and looki...\n\nQ: The court never asked the author's English teacher to give evidence because   _  .", "options": ["the time for the trial was limited to fifteen minutes only", "the author wanted to conduct his own defense in court", "the case was dismissed before the trial reached that stage", "he was found to be unqualified as a character witness"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3368, "question": "One day, I was studying at home . Suddenly, there was a loud noise. I went out of my house to see what had happened . What I saw made me scared. A building in my neighborhood was on fire. Some people were using water to put out the fire; others were rushing towards the building to help put out the fire. The building had three floors. The fire started on the first floor. Soon, it spread to the second floor. There were some people on the second floor at that time. Their lives were in danger. A few people jumped out of the window. Luckily, they only got small injuries. Those who were still on the second floor were just crying for help. The people outside didn't know how to help the people inside to get out. Firefighters arrived at last. They fought the fire bravely. Water pipes were used and ...\n\nQ: How did the people who didn't jump out of the window get out of the building?", "options": ["They were taken out by the firefighters.", "They climbed down a ladder by themselves.", "They walked out of the building after the fire was put out.", "They were taken out by doctors"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 116, "question": "Any high school students lucky enough to be accepted to Harvard University can easily count themselves among the country's best and brightest. The story of David Boone's journey from sleeping on a park bench to one of Harvard's dorm rooms, certainly stands out from the crowd of his peers. David, a 17-year-old senior at a MC2 Stem, a high school in Cleveland, Ohio that focuses largely on engineering and science classes with the help of a grant from the Bill and Melinda Gates Foundation, was offered a full-ride scholarship to Harvard in the fall. His family life has been complicated for the past few years after gangs and economic hardships resulted in him being separated from his family and forced to look after himself on the streets and park benches in Cleveland. Because both his grandmothe...\n\nQ: What's probably the best title for the passage?", "options": ["Chances are there, making an effort to seize them", "Deal with adversity, being determined", "Best way to experience, choosing to be homeless", "From a park bench to a Harvard dormitory An incredible story"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2828, "question": "Are you the kind of person who likes staying in unusual places? If the answer is \"yes\", then try the world's coldest hotel in Jukkasjarvi in the north of Sweden. But go in winter to all you'll find is a pool of water, because the hotel melts every spring! The man who runs the Artic Hall Hotel is Nils Yngve Bergqvist. He built his first ice building for an art exhibition in 1991 and he designed the present hotel-over 200 meters square-himself. It took workmen about two months to pile 1,000 tons of snow onto a wooden base. As the weather got colder, the snow froze and then they removed the base. The whole building and everything in it are made of snow-except for the wooden front door. There's a theatre which Nils uses for a jazz club, a radio station and a large ice bar. As you can imagine, ...\n\nQ: All of the following are true EXCEPT   _  .", "options": ["the hotel costs at least 1,000 tons of snow", "the whole building is made of snow except the wooden front door", "you will receive a survival certificate if you stay in one of the ten ice rooms", "the hotel will fall on a fixed date every year"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 674, "question": "Ben and his wife Susan were on their way to have dinner with their friends. It was a dark,windy night, and they did not know the way very well. They drove through a town until they found what they thought was the road to Dorling,where their friends lived. But it soon became clear that they were not on the road to Dorling at all. The road that they were on was getting narrower,and there were no other cars on it. The wind was blowing harder with every minute that passed. They came to a small village .They drove past a church and then two houses without lights on. There was nobody about to tell them where they were,or where the road went. Just then,Ben saw a telephone box,twenty meters or so further on. While he walked back along the road to see if there was a name outside the church,Susan te...\n\nQ: Some time later Ben and Susan found they took a wrong road because   _  .", "options": ["their friends lived nearer than they drove", "the road was getting narrower and their car alone was on it", "the hard wind made them get lost", "the road was not the same as before"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1658, "question": "Scientists are developing the next generation of robot-driven cars and predict they could be carrying humans around by the year 2030. The first wave of intelligent robot cars, capable of understanding and reacting to the world around them, will be tested this November in a competition run by the US Defense Advanced Research Projects Agency. Scientists are developing vehicles which will not only be driven by robots independently, but will be able to operate in a complicated city environment. \"In the past it was _ for a vehicle just to perceive the environment,\" said Sebastian Thrun, a professor at Stanford University. \"The new challenge will be to understand the environment. The robot must be able to recognize another car, to understand that it is moving and that it will interact with it as...\n\nQ: Compared with the old robot-driven cars, the new ones   _  .", "options": ["can understand orders from humans", "can perceive the environment dearly", "are modified to be completely computer-controllable", "not only can understand the environment but also can react to it"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1237, "question": "Generational differences and the economy are shifting more responsibilities for children from their parents to grandparents, according to a new survey. More than one-third of grandparents aged 50 and older contribute financially to their grandchildren's upbringing, and 11 percent have a grandchild living with them, the poll by AARP, the group for 36 million older US citizens, showed. Forty percent of people who responded to the telephone survey, whose average age was 69, reported spending more than $500 on grandchildren over the past year beyond traditional gifts.Education costs accounted for 53 percent, daily expenses for 37 percent and medical costs for 23 percent.Sixteen percent provided daycare for grandchildren. \"They are the safety net for American families, helping to pay for practi...\n\nQ: The passage mainly tells us   _  .", "options": ["the differences between generations are huge", "how Woelfel Research Inc.conducted the poll", "parents are the safety net for American families", "grandparents take more responsibilities for grandchildren"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1535, "question": "Postcards to myself In 50 years of traveling Colin McCorpuodale has visited every country in the world, except three.And everywhere he goes,he sends himself a postcard.He always chooses a postcard with a beautiful view,and sticks on an interesting stamp.Usually he writes just a short message to himself.His latest one,from the Malians island,read Good fishing. On a wall in his home in London there is a large map of the world.There are hundreds of little red pins stuck in it.\"It's good to get a pin in the map,\" says Mr.McCorquodale, \"but I follow the rules.I'm allowed to stick one in only if I've been in a place for more than 24 hours.\" Naturally,Mr.McCorpuodale has his favorite places.New Zealand he describes as\"wonderful\".In Europe,he says,\"Italy is a favorite place.But in Italy tourists a...\n\nQ: From the passage we know that Mr.McCorpuodale   _  .", "options": ["has visited all the countries in the world", "has only three favorite places", "takes his wife with him wherever he goes", "gets a lot of pleasure from traveling and the planning for it"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 601, "question": "STRANGERS parties go wild these days. The main idea of them is to never let the people know who their matches are until the last minute. These are some popular practices that are storming the world's youth on this V-day. Speed dating It's exactly what the name implies. Complete with a timer, a whistle and 50 willing singles, speed dating is not the traditional dinner and a movie type of first date. Singles pay US $35 for three minutes with more than two dozen future dates. They ask questions and try to get to know each other. At the sound of a whistle, they do the same thing all over again--25 times in all. Lock and key party Women are given a lock and men are given a key, upon arriving at the party. Each key and lock has several matches. One can hunt for his/her later-to-be sweetheart in ...\n\nQ: In which party does a participant have to be careful with the time?", "options": ["Speed dating.", "Lock and key party.", "Dinner in the dark.", "Message party."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2074, "question": "High Speed Book Scanner Simply turning pages of a book quickly may not seem like the best way to scan it. A Japanese research group at Tokyo University has created new software that allows hundreds of pages to be scanned within minutes. Scanning text is normally a boring process with each page having to be inserted into a scanner, but the team led by Professor Masatoshi Ishikawa uses a high speed camera that takes 500 pictures a second to scan pages as they are turned by workers. Normal scanners can only scan the information that is actually before them on the page. This high speed book scanner uses a camera that captures pages at 1000fps as they are turned. A system built in allows it to automatically correct any changes to the text due to the page bending as well as light differences due...\n\nQ: According to Ishikawa, the scanner works by   _   .", "options": ["changing the shape of the images", "reducing the size of the images", "reconstructing the original page", "scanning several pages at the same time"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1758, "question": "I'm part of the Roots & Shoots program founded by Dr. Jane Goodall. The program is intended to make and promote positive changes in the world. As Dr. Goodall says, \"What you do makes a difference, and you have to decide what kind of difference you want to make.\" In Bulgaria, where I live, homeless dogs are everywhere. Many people here turn a blind eye to them. But I cannot ignore the life of a street dog whenever I see one wandering in the street, looking for something to eat. That's why I'm no longer a food waster. When I see wasted food, I always think of a hungry dog climbing to garbage bins, searching for food that people have thrown there. When eating in a restaurant, I'm not afraid to take leftover food to feed stray cats or dogs. A week ago, I saw a homeless dog around the garbage b...\n\nQ: The author uses what Dr. Goodall says to show   _  .", "options": ["how we can develop our business", "why it is important to be great", "why the program is popular globally", "how we can change the world positively"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1801, "question": "Good state is when your body and mind are in the best condition for learning. These pages describe that state. Applying this information will increase your learning performance, without using any of the other techniques on this site. You will learn faster if your cells, body and mind are in good condition, or good \"state.\" Being in good state doesn't just increase your memory and learning performance. Being in good state also helps improve your health and well-being, with resulting benefits in many other areas of your life.The state described on these pages leads to peak condition for performing well in many human endeavors, from flying a plane to playing football. I've grouped the major contributors to Memletic State into three layers. These are the cell, physical and mental state layers....\n\nQ: From the passage, we know that  _  .", "options": ["many other techniques on learning are introduced.", "good learning state refers to mental and physical statement.", "the writer is sure to have a good learning state.", "\"No pains,no gains\" belongs to physcial layer."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1907, "question": "If you want to live longer and lower the risk of heart disease, a move to the mountains may help. Research by scientists in Greece shows that living in the mountains is good for the heart and longevity . People living at higher altitude have lower possibility of dying from heart disease than those closer to sea level, even if they have factors that could increase their risk. \"Residence in mountainous areas seems to have a 'protective effect' from heart disease,\" said Dr Nikos Baibas of the University of Athens. He and his colleagues suspect that the increased exercise from walking up mountainous area gives the heart a good workout and enables it to cope with lower levels of oxygen. Researchers studied the health records and death rates of 1,150 Greeks who lived in three villages near Athen...\n\nQ: Apart from altitude, how many factors raise the chance of developing heart disease?", "options": ["three", "four", "five", "six"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3137, "question": "For some reason, it takes constant reminders that weprimates need nurturing. In a recent study of 46 babychimpanzee orphans, Kim Bard of the University of Portsmouth in England and her colleagues demonstrated that primate babies that have tight relationships with mother figures do much better oncognitive tests than babies who receive only food, shelter, and friendship with peers. But this is not breaking mews. In fact, it's old news. In the 1950s, Harry Harlow conducted a series of experiments with baby monkeys that showed, without doubt, that lack of love and comfort makes for a crazy monkey. Harlow constructed a cage that included a wire monkey \"mother\" topped with a plastic face. In this wire he fixed Mom with a milk bottle. The cage also held another wire mother covered with terry clot...\n\nQ: Which of the following is TURE according to the text?", "options": ["Well-raised chimps always do even better than human kids.", "A 12-month chimps is far cleverer than a child of that age.", "The newborns were not allowed to be with their mothers in the past in the hospital.", "Constantly touching the baby can make it feel safer."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1924, "question": "Ad.1 West High School Bake Sale Come and support our band and buy some delicious baked goods! Friday, September 20th, 2:00 - 4:00 p.m. In the hall by the office after school Cookies: 25 cents each or 5 for $1 Brownies: 50 cents each or 3 for $1.25 Cake by the slice: $1 Whole cakes: $8 Proceeds go toward sending our band to Nationals. Ad.2 SHIPPING AND HANDLING CHARGES Ups or U.S. Parcel Post are the standard methods for continental U.S. shipments. ORDER TOTAL GROUND EXPEDITED GROUND 9-12 working days 4-5 working days $0.00 to $30.00 $4.50 $5.50 $30.01 to $60.00 $7.25 $8.25 $60.01 to $100.00 $9.50 $10.50 $100.01 to $200.00 $11.50 $12.50 Add $7.00 to Ground Rates for 3 Days....\n\nQ: If you wish to receive an order totaling $90.00 within 3 days, how much would the shipping cost?", "options": ["$10.50.", "$15.00.", "$16.50.", "$26.50."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3470, "question": "The story goes that some time ago,a man punished his 3-year-old daughter for wasting a roll of gold wrapping paper.Money was tight and he became infuriated when the child tried to decorate a box to put under the Christmas tree.Nevertheless,the little girl brought the gift to her father the next morning and said,\"This is for you,Daddy.\" The man was embarrassed by his earlier overreaction,but his anger flared again when he found out the box was empty.He yelled at her,stating,\"Don't you know,when you give someone a present,there is supposed to be something inside?\" The little girl looked up at him with tears in her eyes and cried,\"Oh,Daddy,it's not empty at all.I blew kisses into the box.They are all for you,Daddy.\" The father was crushed.He put his arms around his little girl,and he begged f...\n\nQ: The 3-year-old girl was punished by her father for  _  .", "options": ["wasting gold", "wasting gold wrapping paper", "putting the box under the Christmas tree", "bringing the gift to her father"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 215, "question": "The Mysterious Universe By Ellen Jackson and Nic Bishop How did the universe begin? How big is it? What is dark matter? Cosmologist and expert supernova hunter Alex Filippenko hopes that supernovas can help us answer some of these questions. But first we've got to find them! Join Alex and his team as they go on the hunt with huge telescopes and banks of computers. The Time and Space of Uncle Albert By Russell Stannard What would you say if your uncle asked you whether you would like to go into space? You'd say, \"When do I leave?\", just like the girl in this story. Gedanken is speeding across the universe trying to help her uncle answer some questions, such as \"How big is space?\" and \"Where does gravity come from?\" Along the way she also discovers how to get heavier without getting fat, how...\n\nQ: Which book would you read if you want to know about gravity?", "options": ["The Mysterious Universe", "The Time and Space of Uncle Albert", "George's Secret Key to the Universe", "A Child's Introduction to the Night Sky."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3086, "question": "Science isn't something mysterious, only for the few. Every one of us--whether a poet, worker, or physicist has to be able to think scientifically, and to understand some science, such as whether to smoke, what to eat, and what protection to use. Even for decisions that don't depend on some scientific facts, science remains the proven set of best methods for getting exact information about the world. Some people will end up as policy-makers in government or business. People such as these make decisions that affect the life of everyone, and most of them know no more about science than does the rest of the general public. Yet they are called upon to decide what to do about nuclear reactors , global warming, environmental toxins , expensive space programs, and biomedical research. It's nonsci...\n\nQ: What does the author mean by saying that \"a strong scientific spirit is basic to the economy, educational system and society\"?", "options": ["School and society should encourage young people to become professional scientists.", "The school should only teach lessons of economy and education*", "A scientifically educated public is basic to the economy,educational system and society.", "More scientists work in our economy, educational system and society."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 886, "question": "There's a widespread perception in the United States that a university degree is the key to success. But a growing number of educators now say there are other possibilities, especially for students who might not succeed at university level. This is not a traditional classroom. At the apprentice program run by the Plumbers and Steamfitters Union in the state of Maryland, Travis Strawderman and other students make money while they learn. \"I \\t's completely changed my life around,\" he said. \"I've been able to pay off all my debts. I can say I'm actually responsible enough to have my own family.\" Strawderman's five-year program teaches him technical skills free of charge. He says he considered university, but it didn't interest him. Economics Professor Robert Lerman says Strawderman is not alo...\n\nQ: Which might be the best title for the passage?", "options": ["New education programmes", "A University degree, key to success or not", "Problems in high school", "An insurance policy against low wages"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2997, "question": "With my hands and knees on the floor of the airplane, I was searching for an old lady's missing hearing aid during the flight from Sydney to Los Angeles. It occurred to me that this may not be the most dignified posture for a Buddhist nun . I had seen the old lady from the seat in front of me as she walked up and down the passage with a flashlight. I asked a few times what was wrong, but she didn't answer at first --- she couldn't hear me. She was wearing a woolen coat. Judging from her accent, she came from Eastern Europe. Do you know what hearing aids cost? Thousands, especially for the new tiny hidden-in-the-ear type she described. It takes a long time for an appointment to make a new one, and many doctor visits to get the thing adjusted right. Therefore, my dignity seemed less importan...\n\nQ: What do we know about the old lady?", "options": ["She ignored the author's question on purpose.", "She is an American.", "She lost her hearing aid by accident.", "It was not difficult for her to get the hearing aid at all."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2207, "question": "The picture-like island is rich in scenic beauty. Barbados sightseeing is a photographer's dream that comes true with numbers of natural wonders, breathtaking scenic views, attractive gardens and miles of white, sandy beaches. There's so many things to see and to do, as you check out some of the places of interest on the island. Historical Appeal Experience Full of historical appeal you'll love the impressive collection of beautiful great houses, landmarks, old churches, and traditional ancient houses some of which may date back to the 16th century. Historic Bridgetown, over 375 years old, capital of Barbados, is located with its color1ful fishing boats and splendid yachts ( ) . Check out the Barbados National and see some of the island's most beautiful homes. Nature Charm Enjoyment Nature...\n\nQ: What should be the best title for the passage?", "options": ["A Car Adventure of Touring Barbados with Fun", "An Island of Historical Appeal as One Expects", "Barbados-A Wonderful Place for Sightseeing", "Return to Nature, Know More of the Bajans"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1044, "question": "Children will find it more difficult to buy cigarettes as vending machines selling tobacco will be officially banned in England today.According to the British Heart Foundation(BHF),around 200,000 young people start smoking regularly in England each year and 11 per cent of l1-to15-year-old regular smokers in England and Wales get their cigarettes from vending machines. Betty McBride, Director of Policy and Communications at the British Heart Foundation,said,\"Thousands of children who are at risk of addiction regularly get tobacco from these machines,which of course,don't ask them to prove their age.With the tobacco industry increasingly depending on young smokers to keep their profits,they're fighting tooth and nail to stop any changes that might hit their bottom line.\" The ban, which makes...\n\nQ: Small stores in Scotland   _", "options": ["will be banned from selling tobacco next year", "can still present cigarettes for around 2 years", "must get rid of all tobacco advertisements", "must show warnings about cigarettes in 2013"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3231, "question": "Global warming is causing more than 300,000 deaths and about $125 billion in economic losses each year, according to a report by the Global Humanitarian Forum, an organization led by Annan, the former United Nations secretary general. The report, to be released Friday, analyzed data and existing studies of health, disaster, population and economic trends. It found that human-influenced climate change was raising the global death rates from illnesses including malnutrition and heat-related health problems. But even before its release, the report drew criticism from some experts on climate and risk, who questioned its methods and conclusions. Along with the deaths, the report said that the lives of 325 million people, primarily in poor countries, were being seriously affected by climate chan...\n\nQ: What does Kofi Annan say should be the focus of the Copenhagen conference?", "options": ["How rich and poor regions can share responsibility in curbing global warming.", "How human and economic losses from climate change can be reduced.", "How emissions of heat-trapping gases can be reduced on a global scale.", "How rich countries can better help poor regions reduce climate hazards."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2366, "question": "All the oceans of the world will be dead in the future unless action is taken at once. How can this happen? We have already seen that people allow all sorts of waste products to flow into the sea. It is almost impossible to measure how much waste water and industrial waste in our oceans, but we can find out how much oil is poured into them legally and illegally. It is illegal to pour oil into the sea close to the shore, but when a ship is many miles out to sea, there are no such rules. Scientists have different ideas as to the amount of oil putting into the sea, but the lowest figure for oil poured in European waters alone is nearly 200 000 tons every year. Some people say the figure could be ten times as high. It is not only our coasts that suffer from oil pollution. Many shell fish, for ...\n\nQ: According to the passage, what is the main cause of oil pollution?", "options": ["Oil ships which meet and strike each other.", "Oil poured at sea when the oil tanks are cleaned out.", "Oil from waste water and industrial waste.", "Oil coming out of the bottom of the sea."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3196, "question": "Pingviman Hotel Offering an outdoor pool, Pingviman Hotel offers Thai-style rooms in Chiang Mai. Free WiFi is available through-out and a complimentary service takes guests to the Chiang Mai Night Bazaar. All rooms are equipped with a 48-inch flat-screen cable TV and DVD player. Facilities at this hotel include a business center, a fitness center and laundry services. There is also a tour desk and meeting facilities. We speak your language! Hotel Rooms:35 Art Mai Gallery Nimman Hotel Situated in Chiang Mai's trendiest area, Art Mai Gallery Nimman Hotel Chiang Mai by Compass Hospitality boasts accommodation in a boutique hotel well-decorated with art works from the renowned local Thai artists. Free WiFi is offered all throughout the property. At Art Mai Gallery Nimman Hotel, guests will fin...\n\nQ: In which hotels can guests book a trip more conveniently?", "options": ["Pingviman Hotel and De Chai Hotel.", "Art Mai Gallery Nimman Hotel and At Chiang Mai.", "Pingviman Hotel and At Chiang Mai.", "Art Mai Gallery Nimman Hotel and De Chai Hotel."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 281, "question": "Chinese New Year celebrations, also known as the Spring Festival start on the 23rd day of the 12th lunar month of the Chinese calendar, and end on the 15th day of the first lunar month in the following year in the Chinese calendar. Chinese New Year's Day's date is calculated according to the Chinese lunar calendar. In 2015 it's Thursday, February 19. Many people clean their homes to welcome the Spring Festival. They put up the red posters with poetic verses on it to their doors, Chinese New Year pictures on their walls, and decorate their homes with red lanterns. It is also a time to reunite with s so many people visit their families at this time of the year. In the evening of the Spring Festival Eve, many people set off fireworks and firecrackers, hoping to cast away any bad luck and brin...\n\nQ: Traditionally Chinese New Year will last about", "options": ["23 days", "15 days", "7 days", "25 days"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3061, "question": "China, known as the \"kingdom of bicycle\", will see a quick growth in electric bicycle production in the next five years thanks to the country's efforts to save energy and improve the environment. The output of electric bikes is expected to maintain an annual growth rate of at least 80 percent in the coming five years. China will _ 30 million electricity-driven bikes in 2020, compared to 9 million bikes last year, according to a report from the Development Research Center under the State Council and other ministries such as the National Development and Reform Commission. The central government wants to reduce the amount of energy consumption by as much as 20 percent within the next five years. That would be achieved through the introduction of new sources of energy and encouraging people to...\n\nQ: We can learn from the passage that   _  .", "options": ["China will produce 9 million electricity-driven bikes in 2020", "the central government of China wants to increase the amount of energy consumption", "China is the world's second biggest producer, consumer and exporter of the energy-efficient vehicle", "the output of electric bikes is expected to increase at least 80 percent in the coming five years"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3156, "question": "The British policeman has several nicknames, but the most frequently used are\"copper\"and\"bobby\". The first name comes from the verb \"cop\" meaning \"to take\" or \"capture\", and thesecond comes from the first name of Sir Robert Peel, a 19th century politician, who was the founder of the police force. An early nickname for the policeman was \"peeler\", but this name had died out. Visitors to England seem,nearly always, to be very impressed by the English police. In fact, it has become a joke that the visitors to Britain, when asked for his views of the country, will always say,at some point or other, \"I think your policemen are wonderful.\" Well, the British bobby may not always be wonderful but he is usually a very friendly and helpful character. A music-hall song of some years ago was called, \"I...\n\nQ: \"If you want to know the time, ask a policeman.\" That means   _   .", "options": ["the British policeman is friendly and helpful", "the British policeman has plenty of time to help people", "people usually think that the policeman always knows the time", "it is a duty for the policeman to tell people the time"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3198, "question": "Pingviman Hotel Offering an outdoor pool, Pingviman Hotel offers Thai-style rooms in Chiang Mai. Free WiFi is available through-out and a complimentary service takes guests to the Chiang Mai Night Bazaar. All rooms are equipped with a 48-inch flat-screen cable TV and DVD player. Facilities at this hotel include a business center, a fitness center and laundry services. There is also a tour desk and meeting facilities. We speak your language! Hotel Rooms:35 Art Mai Gallery Nimman Hotel Situated in Chiang Mai's trendiest area, Art Mai Gallery Nimman Hotel Chiang Mai by Compass Hospitality boasts accommodation in a boutique hotel well-decorated with art works from the renowned local Thai artists. Free WiFi is offered all throughout the property. At Art Mai Gallery Nimman Hotel, guests will fin...\n\nQ: What can't guests do in the hotel according to the passage?", "options": ["Have meals at the restaurant of At Chiang Mai 24 hours.", "Have their clothes washed in At Chiang Mai.", "Have a meeting in Pingviman Hotel.", "Do massage in Art mai Gallery Nimman Hotel."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2389, "question": "Here are some of the best movies you like. I believe they can accompany you to spend your dull weekend. In this story a computer hacker searches for the truth behind the mysterious force . In the 22nd century it turns out that the world is controlled by a magic computer system called the Matrix and people live in an unreal world. The computer hacker and his comrades overcome much difficulty and at last find the way to take over the Matrix and save the world. This comedy is about J and K, agents in a top secret agency , and they fight bravely with the alien to save the galaxy from a bad-tempered alien \"bug\" and save the Earth from being destroyed . Harry has lived under the stairs at his aunt and uncle's house. But on his 11th birthday, he learns he's a powerful wizard----with a place waiti...\n\nQ: Harry Potter    _   .", "options": ["does't know he's a powerful wizard until he is 11 years old", "has a happy and pleasant childhood with his aunt and uncle", "hates to stay at the Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry", "Knows how his parents died before he goes to the Hogwarts school"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2831, "question": "It has been argued that an infant under three who is cared for outside the home may suffer because of the separation from his parents.The British psychoanalyst John Bowlby believes that separation from the parents during the sensitive \"attachment\" period from birth to three may scar a child's personality and incline to emotional problems in later life.Some people have drawn the conclusion from Bowlby's work that children should not be sent to day care before the age of three, and many people do believe this.But there are also arguments against such a strong conclusion. Firstly, anthropologists point out that the hidden love between children and parents found in modem societies does not usually exist in traditional societies.For example, we saw earlier that among the Ngonis the father and m...\n\nQ: According to Bowlby, children under the age of three  _  .", "options": ["should not be sent to school", "should be cared for outside the home", "will not suffer fro m parental separation", "don't mind who will look after them"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1302, "question": "Signing up for a digital TV service provides you with access to over 200 channels from all over the globe. However, television today is dominated by adult language, making it hard for concerned families to find channels suitable for young eyes. Therefore, most movie channels are automatically removed form the list of TV channels for an entire family. The following are some good ones based on popularity on a global scale. Discovery Channel Discovery and its many channels can be considered as the founding father of informative channels on television. What National Geographic does in a scholastic manner, Discovery tries to do in an entertaining manner--educating the masses about anything and everything. Fox Family Finding a movie channel that broadcasts pictures suitable for teenagers and kid...\n\nQ: According to the text, most channels offered by a digital TV service   _  .", "options": ["can keep people away from TV violence", "are welcomed by families with small children", "are concerned about the proper use of language", "are unsuitable for the whole family to watch together"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 145, "question": "Growing up in Philadelphia, Lieberman started cooking with his stay-at-home dad when he was seven. His food-loving family had two kitchens, and he quickly learned what was the best way to bake his cakes. Lieberman improved his kitchen skills during a year abroad beforo college, learning from a cook in Italy and study local specialties in Gerrnany, Spain and France. At Yale,he was known for throwing dinner parties, single-handedly frying and baking while mixing drinks for dozens offriends. Just for fun, he and some friends decided to tape a show named Campus Cuisine about his cooking. Lieberman was a real college student showing his classmate how to do things like making drinks out of dining-hall fruit. That helped the show become very popular among the students. They would stop Lieberman a...\n\nQ: We can learn from the text that Lieberman's family  _  .", "options": ["have relatives in Europe", "love cooking at home", "often hold parties", "own a restaurant"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1626, "question": "Nick Vujicic was born with no arms or legs, but he doesn't let this stop him. The brave 26-year-old man plays football and golf, and swims, in spite of the fact that he has no arms or legs. Nick has a small foot on his left side, which helps him balance and makes him able to kick. He uses his one foot to type, write with a pen and pick things up. \"I call it my chicken drumstick ,\" joked Nick, who was born in Melbourne, Australia, but now lives in Los Angeles. \"I'd be lost without it. When I get in the water I float because 80 percent of my body is lungs and my drumstick acts as a propeller .\" \"He's very modest, but he gets marriage proposals from women all the time,\" said Nick's friend Steve Appel. \"He would love to get married and start a family, but he's waiting for the right girl to com...\n\nQ: We can learn from the text that Nick   _  .", "options": ["has a poor sense of balance", "understands his mother very well", "considers his small foot ugly", "is disappointed with his health condition"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 354, "question": "I love everything about making Easter dinner except the Saturday shopping. That day, the supermarket can be as crowded as a department store at Christmas. And this Easter, on top of my regular checklist, I had to buy the ingredient for a delicious, new recipe I'd discovered: sliced ham and turkey layered with Swiss cheese and cabbage, all wrapped in pastry dough. Trouble was that my work schedule had left me no time to shop earlier in the week. I would get up extra early and take care of everything on Saturday morning, I thought, as I drove to the office on Friday. But that morning, Yola, one of my co-workers, asked if my husband Robert and I would help her move the next day. \"I really don't have anybody else to ask,\" she apologized. \"Sure,\" I told her, soft touch that I am. Early Saturday...\n\nQ: Why did Yola give the author food?", "options": ["The food she bought was too much to eat up.", "She knew that the author liked eating the food.", "She was leaving and feared the food would go to waste.", "She knew that the author didn't buy Easter food."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3250, "question": "Most people buy a lot of gifts just before Christmas. But some people think we buy too much. They have started a special day called Buy Nothing Day. They don't want anyone to go shopping on that day. Buy Nothing Day is November 29. It's 25 days before Christmas. It's after Thanksgiving Day and often the first day of Christmas shopping. At this time, we see ads in Newspapers and on TV telling us to \"buy, buy, buy!\" The idea for Buy Nothing Day started in Vancouver, British Columbia. Now people all over the world celebrate Buy Nothing Day. In California, parents and children get together to read stories, sing songs, and paint pictures. The children talk about why they don't need a lot of toys. This year, in Manchester, England, people dressed up in costumes to tell people that we buy too muc...\n\nQ: People usually buy many gifts  _  .", "options": ["before Thanksgiving", "on Christmas", "before Christmas", "anytime"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3493, "question": "Do you know how to play a game called \"Musical Chairs\"?It is easy to play and most people enjoy it. All you need are some chairs, some people and some way of making music. You may use a piano or any other musical instrument, if someone can play it. You may use a tape recorder. You can even use a radio. Put the chairs in a row. The chairs may be put in twos, back to back. A better way is to have the chairs in one row with each chair facing in the opposite direction to the chair next to it. The game is easy. When the music starts, the players walk round the chairs. Everyone goes in the same direction, of course, they should walk in time to the music. If the music is fast they should walk quickly. If the music is slow, they should walk slowly. The person playing music cannot see the people in...\n\nQ: If ten people are playing musical chairs,you must begin with   _  .", "options": ["nine chairs", "ten chairs", "eleven chairs", "one chair"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 586, "question": "Some mothers in Senegal are learning a new way to save the lives of babies born too soon. The idea is borrowed from the way mother kangaroos carry their young in front in a pouch. The baby kangaroo stays in this built-in baby carrier until it can survive independently. Kangaroo mother care is also known as the skin-to-skin method for premature babies. The direct contact with the mother keeps the baby warm. It also lets the baby breastfeed at any time. The mother's heartbeat also helps control the baby's breathing rate. Every year, seven thousand babies are born at the health center where Ousmane Ndiaye works in Guediaway, outside Dakar. One in five is underweight. But Senegal has few incubators in which to keep premature babies warm. In Africa, one newborn in twenty dies. A major reason is...\n\nQ: What is the major reason for the high death rates of newborns in Africa?", "options": ["They are not fed with nutritious food", "Most hospitals don't have incubators", "The newborns are not taken good care of", "They are born before the usual time"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3317, "question": "In the past ten years, America's National Basketball Association (NBA) has grown increasingly dependent on the rest of the world to supply players. When Michael Jordan and Larry Bird won gold in Barcelona in 1992, the Americans were praised for teaching the world how to play basketball. This season, however, 20 percent of NBA rosters will be filled by non-Americans. NBA commissioner David Stem happily embraces the trend. On a visit to Paris in October, Stern outlined his vision for the future, which is likely to see Europe hosting NBA games by 2010. The NBA is now planning to _ . \"Our experience in China has been that it is going to be explosive in its growth,\"said Stem. The strategy (,)in China is television.\"We've made 14 deals in China with local and national networks on cable and satel...\n\nQ: Which of the following can be used as the best title for the passage?", "options": ["The Non-American Basketball Players", "NBA Is Coming to China", "The Foreign Ties That Bind the NBA", "NBA Is Making Big Progress"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 779, "question": "The Pew report,which was based on surveys carried out in Britain,France,Germany, Italy,Spain,Greece, Poland and the Czech Republic,said that the European Union was \"the new sick man of Europe\".The percentage of Europeans with a good view of the EU has fallen from 60 percent last year to 45 percent now. The UK may be considered the most Eurosceptic country ,but its support for the Union has barely changed in the past 1 2 months,falling only two points to 43 percent.But,France's backing for the EU has fallen sharply,from 60 percent last year to 41 percent today. On the question of whether to remain in the EU, 46 percent of the British want to leave the Union and surprisingly,the same percentage want to stay. The Pew report's authors said, \"The long-term economic crisis has created bad forces...\n\nQ: As to whether to remain in the EU,  _   .", "options": ["Britons are divided equally", "few Britons want to stay", "all Britons support to leave", "Britons don't care about it"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 267, "question": "Over the years, Brian Wansink, director of the Food and Brand Lab at Cornell University, has studied such things as how far Americans typically drive to buy food, how many times we refill our plates at all-you-can-eat buffets and how we organize our kitchens. In the mid-2000s he famously coined the phrase \"mindless eating\"(and wrote a book by that name) to focus attention on all the bad dietary decisions we make without really thinking about them. His new book, Slim by Design: Mindless Eating Solutions for Everyday Life, aims to change the design of restaurants, school lunchrooms, office cafeterias and homes so that the mindless choices we make will be more healthful ones. Some examples: Keep kitchen counters clear. No visible snack food, no bread, no nuts--not even breakfast cereal. In Wa...\n\nQ: What's the main idea of the passage?", "options": ["Changing environment or habits of eating will help you eat less.", "Eating fruits and vegetables is better for your health.", "Keeping your kitchen counter clear of any food will help make you thin.", "Many people eat or drink too much without paying attention to it."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 350, "question": "Forget Twitter and Facebook, Google and the Kindle. Television is still the most influential medium around. Indeed, for many of the poorest regions of the world, it remains the next big thing--finally becomes globally available. And that is a good thing, because the TV revolution is changing lives for the better. Across the developing world, around 45% of families had a TV in 1995; by 2005 the number had climbed above 60% . That is some way behind the U.S. ,where there are more TVs than people, and where people now easily get access to the Internet. Five million more families in sub-Saharan Africa will get a TV over the next five years. In 2005 , after the fall of the Taliban ,which had banned TV, I in 5 Afghans had one. The global total is another 150 million by 2013--pushing the numbers ...\n\nQ: The author intends to   _  .", "options": ["stress the advantages of TV to people's lives", "persuade women to become more independent", "encourage people to improve their reading skills", "introduce the readers some websites such as Google"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1883, "question": "The man from the west stopped and drew back his arm. \"You're not Jimmy Wells,\" he said in a quick and angry way, \"Twenty years is a long time, but not long enough to change a man' nose from a Roman to pug.\" \"It sometimes changes a good man into a bad one,\" said the tall man, \"you've been under arrest for ten minutes. Silky Bob. prefix = st1 /Chicagothinks you may have dropped over our way and phones us she wants to have a word with you. Going quietly, are you? That's sensible. Now before we go to the station here's a note I was asked to hand you. You may read it here at the window. It's from Patrolman Wells.?\" The man from the West opened the little piece of paper handed him. His hand was steady when he began to read, but it trembled a little by the time he finished. The note was rather sh...\n\nQ: The two men may have walked   _  .", "options": ["for ten minutes", "arm in arm", "face to face", "both A and B"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1419, "question": "Farmer Joe was in his cart when he was hit by a truck. He decided his injuries from the accident were serious enough to take the trucking company to court. In court the trucking company's lawyer was questioning farmer Joe. \"Didn't you say, at the scene of the accident, 'I'm fine'?\" said the lawyer. Farmer Joe responded, \"Well, I'll tell you what happened. I had just loaded my favorite donkey Bessie into the....\" \"I didn't ask for any details,\" the lawyer interrupted, \"just answer the question. Didn't you say, at the scene of the accident, 'I'm fine'?\" Farmer Joe said, \"Well I had just got Bessie into the cart and I was driving down the road....\" The lawyer interrupted again and said, \"Judge, I am trying to establish the fact that, at the scene of the accident, this man told the highway pol...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements is TRUE, according to the passage?", "options": ["Farmer Joe tried to cover the fact in the court but no one would believe him.", "Farmer Joe couldn't have said \"I' m fine\" at the scene of the accident.", "Farmer Joe couldn't remember whether he had said \"I'm fine\" at the scene of the accident.", "Farmer Joe did say \"I'm fine\" at the scene of the accident."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1681, "question": "It was a warm April day when a big fat envelope came in the mail from the only college I had ever imagined attending. I tore open the packet. My eyes were fixed on the word \"congratulations. \"I don't remember ever smiling so wide. Then I looked at my financial package. The cost of Dream School's tuition , room and board was around $ 40,000- an impossible sum! How could I afford to attend? What good reasons did I have to go there when three other fine colleges were offering me free tuition? My other choices were good, solid schools even if they weren't as famous as my first choice. In my mind, attending my dream university would be the only way to realize my dream of becoming a world-class writer. My parents understood how I felt. They told me that even though it would be a financial proble...\n\nQ: How did the author feel when he started to read the letter?", "options": ["He was lost in his dream.", "He was full of joy.", "He was worried about the money.", "He was uncertain which school to go to."], "answer": 1}]